trumpia.com 2008-05-20

# Mobile Text, Instant Message, Email, and Mobile Keyword: All-In-One Marketing by Trumpia

Trumpia reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify or change this Privacy Policy at any time with or without prior notice to you. You should review the current Privacy Policy on a regular basis. The date of the last update will be posted at the top of this Privacy Policy for your convenience. Your continued use of the Trumpia service following the posting of any changes to the Privacy Policy constitutes your full acceptance of those changes. If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about this Privacy Policy, you may email us at [Contact@MyTrum.com](mailto:contact@mytrum.com).

Trumpia provides its customers (also referred to as "you") the tools and resources to collect your subscribers' contact info on an opt-in basis. **NOTE:** Receiving mobile text messages from Trumpia is completely FREE of charge; however, standard text messaging rates from wireless providers still apply. **

Express Sign Up

**

Trumpia allows you to collect email addresses, instant message screen names, and mobile phone numbers when subscribers opt-in to join your distribution list(s) via an Express Sign Up page powered by Trumpia. When joining a distribution list, we will ask subscribers for personal information such as their name, mobile phone number, IM screen name, email address, and optional password. The information they provide and the information Trumpia obtains about them may be used to: 

  * Provide subscribers with products and services they request.
  * To anticipate and resolve problems and conflicts with our products and services.
  * For verification and authentication purposes in regards to requests or changes of any personal information or data related.
  * For other purposes communicated to them at the time they provide or authorize the use of their information.

Trumpia provides subscribers the opportunity to opt-in, opt-out or change their settings via a link in the footer of email and IM messages. These options are made available when people sign in at an Express Sign Up page. **

Mobile Keyword

**

In addition to Express Sign Up pages, you can also collect mobile phone numbers when subscribers text your Mobile Keyword (that you create) to Trumpia's short code (69302). By texting your Mobile Keyword, subscribers are opting-in their mobiles phones to join your distribution list(s). They are also giving implied consent for you to send them text messages and to allow you to view and access their mobile phone numbers. A subscriber can remove their mobile phone number from your database at anytime by replying to any text message they receive from Trumpia with "STOP".

Trumpia is the sole owner of all contact info collected on this site - both your contact info and your subscribers' contact info. A "subscriber" is defined as any person who has opted-in to receive messages from you via an Express Sign Up page or Mobile Keyword. 

Trumpia does not share, sell, or rent any contact info with third parties for their promotional use unless we have explicit or implied consent from the owners of such contact info. An implied consent is when your subscribers text your Mobile Keyword to Trumpia's short code (69302). In this case, your subscribers' contact info may be shared with you. However, if the subscriber logs into his/her own subscription management account at anytime and unchecks this permission, the contact information (mobile number) will not be viewable or exportable. 

An explicit consent is when subscribers place a checkmark next to a statement that permits you to view their direct contact info. This checkmark option for the subscribers to share their info with you can be found on every Express Sign Up page powered by Trumpia. 

Trumpia allows you to view and export your subscribers' contact information as long as you have received implied or explicit consent from them. Refer to the paragraphs above. No contact information will be shared without first obtaining permission.   
**  
NOTE:** Whether explicit or implied, you are not allowed to share your subscribers' contact info with any third party for any reason. Also, Trumpia may use or disclose information, including your personal info and your subscribers' contact info, under the following very limited circumstances: 

  * To enforce our Terms of Use or other legal agreements. 
  * To outsource any of the tasks referenced in this Privacy Policy, such as billing, customer service, or responding to inquiries.
  * In response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process.
  * To establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * To a company controlled by, or under common control with, Trumpia for any purpose permitted by this Privacy Policy. 
  * When Trumpia believes such use or disclosure is (a) necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or (b) required by law.
  * In the event of a merger, acquisition, consolidation, divestiture, or bankruptcy of Trumpia.

**NOTE:** The Trumpia service is not intended for children under 13, and Trumpia does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.
